=Episode 17=
No.
You must be mistaken.
Jin Yunlie could never be
the Huyun Deity.
He's the Crown Prince of Huyun,
beloved by his people.
You've been deceived by his appearance.
No.
I trust my instincts and my heart.
(I'm from Longyuan Kingdom.)
(I was cast out of Huangyan Kingdom!)
(Xuanhan Kingdom exiled me!)
(Stay behind me.)
He could never be the cruel,
merciless Huyun Deity you speak of.
More importantly,
I love him.
I will never let you kill him.
It's not him?
But
the resemblance is uncanny.
Very well.
Xi Yuan,
I'll trust you this once.
But you should know
I only have enough power
to get you out of here.
I can't save both of you.
I will never abandon him.
Just as
he would never abandon me.
Jin Yunlie,
I'm coming to save you.
That's the Phoenix Primordial Flame!
Xi Yuan.
Xi Yuan, get out of here!
Leave me!
Don't talk nonsense.
How could I ever leave you behind?
Just a moment.
Just a moment longer.
So what if you wield
the Phoenix Primordial Flame?
Today,
no one can stop me.
Xi Yuan!
Jin Yunlie...
Gu Diao,
I'll kill you!
Madman!
You've truly gone mad!
You've actually fallen into
to demonic corruption.
I once suppressed your master.
Today, I can kill you too.
Jin Yunlie,
don't try anything,
or I'll kill her.
Gu Diao,
now!
Reversal of Heaven and Earth!
Jin Yunlie!
Die!
Jin Yunlie,
in the end, you still died by my hand.
wake up! Please!
I'm here! I'm here!
I've come to save you.
Jin Yunlie!
Jin Yunlie...
Jin Yunlie, please, wake up!
I...
I've come to save you.
I'm here to save you.
Wake up...
Jin Yunlie,
wake up.
Jin Yunlie, don't scare me like this.
Jin Yunlie...
Jin Yunlie, you can't die!
Don't die!
Please, don't die!
Jin Yunlie,
don't leave me behind.
Don't go...
No!
Jin Yunlie...
You have come at last.
Phoenix Deity,
you're a deity.
Please, save him. I beg you.
Please, save him!
It's useless.
He's already dead.
His soul is probably already
at the River of Oblivion.
The River of Oblivion?
Then I'll go there and find him!
You're still in a mortal body.
You can't withstand
the Death Energy of the Netherworld.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless
you can rebuild your phoenix form
and obtain the power
of rebirth through nirvana.
At that point,
the Life Energy you can wield
will counter all
Demonic Energy and Death Energy.
Nirvana...
You don't have much time left.
Have you made your decision?
I'm willing to undergo nirvana.
Nirvana
means reliving
your most agonizing memories of death
thousands of times.
Only by enduring it all
can you become
the true immortal phoenix.
So she couldn't make it after all?
How did she suddenly die?
How am I supposed to report this
to the Great Demon Lord now?
That's...
How can there be
a remnant soul inside her body?
Trying to flee?
Not a chance.
Xi Yuan,
I can only stall him for a moment.
You have to make it through nirvana.
Xi Yuan,
you have to hold on.
How could
a fragment of his divine sense be here?
Xi Yuan.
Xi Yuan?
Wake up.
Jin Yunlie?
Jin Yunlie,
aren't you already dead?
Why are you here?
I really am dead.
What you see now
is a fragment of my divine sense
I left inside you
during the Martial Trial.
Jin Yunlie,
can you please stay?
Can you stay with me a little longer?
I want to stay with you too.
But I believe
that even without me,
you can keep living, and live well.
So,
for me,
please don't give up.
Jin Yunlie!
No!
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit,
the envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions,
leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road,
I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain,
forever beyond redemption♪